Let's apply what we just learned by opening up
the MainActivity.java file within our project. We're going to take
this networking code snippet and move it over to
it's own AsyncTask, so it runs in a background
thread. The task is going to be defined within
this fragment class. But speaking of which, it's actually
still called PlaceholderFragment. Let's do a little bit of
refactoring now by giving it a real name. Let's call
it ForecastFragment. And then you can update it
in other appropriate places as well. We can also
move ForecastFragment into its own file that way
the MainActivity won't get so long and cumbersome. Within
ForecastFragment we should define a new inner class
called FetchWeatherTask which extends from AsyncTask. And then you
can move the networking code snippet here. After you
make the changes and run your app, it should
look something like this. There really should be no difference except it
doesn't crash now. In the next step we will add code to execute
the task. And later in the lesson, we'll do JSON parsing and updating
the UI. In the meantime though, make these initial changes to your code.